{
    "id": "21481a2089c347679b131c811f1899c3",
    "title": "First conditional sentences exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "edbfd366375640bd8af932a71d170343",
            "title": "First Conditional Forms Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "If I see Jennie, I …………………………. her your love.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will give",
                        "would give",
                        "would have given"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Oil ………………………. if you pour it on water.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "floats",
                        "will float",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "If she …………………………….. to us, then we will have to go and see her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "can't come",
                        "couldn't come"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you ………………………… to learn a second language, you have to work hard.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "want",
                        "wanted",
                        "had wanted"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you eat too much, you ………………………… fat.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will get",
                        "would get",
                        "would have gotten"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "If I know her name, I …………………………. you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will tell",
                        "would tell",
                        "would have told"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will be absolutely happy, if I …………………………… a car.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "have",
                        "had"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "What will you do, if you ………………….. your job.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "lose",
                        "lost",
                        "had lost"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "If we ……………………… a map, we will be able to get out of here.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "have",
                        "had"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will get up earlier if there ……………………….. a good reason to.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "was"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}